https://duplagadev.vercel.app/

+48 780 106 771

- Pawelduplagait@gmail.com
- Wrocław, Dolnoślaskie

Summary

As a Full-stack Developer with 2 years of commercial experience, I am well-versed in object-oriented programming and have a good understanding of frontend technologies. I have recently been focusing on improving my Next. js skills, particularly in server-side rendering.

github.com/PawelDuplaga



in linkedin.com/in/pawelduplaga

Skills

Next.js, React, Redux, Zustand, Prisma, Cypress, HTML, CSS, SASS, Tailwind, Typescript, JavaScript, C#, .NET, Entity Framework, Python, Git, Microservices, REST API, Unity, PostgreSQL, MongoDb

Education

Wrocław University of Science and Technology (Politechnika Wrocławska)

- Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science 06/2022
- Bachelor thesis Evolutionary Optization of Algorithms Controlling Non-Playable Characters in Games (C#, Unity)

Throughout my education, I gained proficiency in several programming languages, including Java, Python, C++, C#, Scala, Ocaml, and JavaScript. Additionally, I completed multiple coursework in project management and software engineering.

Experience

Rigby · Frontend Engineer (freelance)

08/2023 - Present

Next.js, React, Typescript, Javascript, HTML, SCSS, E-commerce, Headless CMS, Figma

I contributed to the development of e-commerce solutions for clients such as Unitra (Unitra.com) and Platyna Marketplace (Platyna.pl). My responsibilities included webapp page development and seamless integration of Medusa.js headless CMS with the web applications. In this projects I was focused on providing rapid performance of these webapps, prioritizing a good customer experience.

Devnet · Software Engineer

05/2022 - 08/2023

.NET, Python, PostgreSQL, MongoDb, RabbitMq, Azure, React, Microservices, Design patterns

I contributed to a project aimed at creating software for automated energy trading within European markets, by maintaining and expanding the system by developing new microservices. My notable accomplishment involved creating a Python script for complex data manipulation, optimizing testing processes. This efficiency improvement resulted in cost savings and allowed us to allocate more time to address real-time challenges.

Sellintegro · C# Junior Engineer

07/2021 - 10/2021

.NET, SQL, Vbscript, Javascript, Docker

I played a key role in the development of a product that facilitated the integration of e-commerce and ERP systems. I joined specialized division of the company dedicated to delivering premium customer service to our largest clients. Within this team, I directly engaged with clients and crafted tailored software solutions to meet their unique requirements.

Languages: Polish (native), Eglish (C2)

Hobbies: Basketball, Technology, Modern design, Architecture